Timeless Love is a drama, romance, tv movie film directed by Brian Brough.
Megan seems to have the perfect life with a wonderful
husband named Thomas and 2 adorable children.
Then she finds herself awakening from a coma - and
discovers she is not and has never been married.
But when she meets Thomas for real, she seizes the chance to help
him fall in love with her, again-for the first time.
Megan Murphy, played by Rachel Skarsten.
Thomas, played by Brant Daugherty.
Debra Murphy, played by Jill Adler.
Eve, played by Liz Christensen.
Dr. Yates, played by Scott Christopher.
Patrick Clayborne, played by Rick Macy.
Abigail Leigh Spencer (born August 4, 1981) is an
American actress, producer and writer.
She began her career playing Rebecca Tyree on the ABC daytime television soap opera All My Children
(1999–2001) before going on to star in the Lifetime crime drama series, Angela's Eyes (2006).
From 2013 to 2016, Spencer starred as Amantha Holden in the SundanceTV drama series Rectify, for which she received a nomination for a
Critics' Choice Television Award; she then starred as history professor Lucy Preston in the NBC science-fiction series Timeless.
In 2026 she aired in a lead role in the FOX series Best Medicine.
Spencer has appeared in many films, including In My Sleep (2010), Cowboys & Aliens (2011), This Means War (2012), Chasing Mavericks (2012), The
Haunting in Connecticut 2: Ghosts of Georgia (2013), Oz the Great and Powerful (2013), and This Is Where I Leave You (2014).
She also had recurring roles on the series Mad Men (2009), Hawthorne
(2009–2011), Suits (2011–2019), and Grey's Anatomy (2017–2022).
The tone is emotional and intense.